Guide to the Bobbye S. Ortiz Papers, 1919-1993 and undated (bulk 1950-1990) RL.00978
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Phonograph Records Series, [195-]-[198-] and undated
  - Twelve Inch Recordings
    - Italy
      - #106 Title: Canti di donne in lotta: Il canzoniere femminista
        - Performer: Gruppo Musicale del Comitato per il Salario al Lavoro Domestico (Box 43)
          Side 1: Prologo, Siamo stufe, E la mi mamma, Canzone di strada, Devento mata, Avete mai guardato, Il parto, Noi donne
          Side 2: Bambini pianificati, Il divorzio, La malcontenta, Aborto di stato, Stornello per i compagni; Stato, padroni...
          Record Label: I Dischi Dello Zodiaco, VPA 8259
      - #107 Title: I Gufi cantano due secoli di resistenza (Box 43)
        Side 1: Partire, partir, partir bisogna; Inno a Oberdan, Addio a Lugano, Ninna nanna della guerra, O Gorizia tu sei maledetta, Il bersagliere ha cento penne
        Side 2: Bella ciao, Fischia il vento, Cosa rimiri mio bel partigiano, Piet l' morta, Se non ci ammazza i crucchi
        Record Label: Columbia, QPX 8093
      - #108 Title: La vivazione: La partita truccata
        - Performer: Giovanna Marini (Box 43)
          Side 1/2: Canta e suona: Poema epico
          Record Label: CEDI, GLP 81023
      - #109 Title: Non consumiamo Marx
        - Performer: Luigi Nono (Box 43)
          Side 1: Un Volto, Del mare
          Side 2: Non consumiamo Marx
          Record Label: I Dischi del Sole, DS 182/84/CL
      - #110 Title: Palmiro Togliatti: La sua voce, il suo pensiero, le sue testimonianze di protagonista (Box 43)
        Sides 1/2: La svolta di Salerno
        Record Label: Della S.P.A.M., GLP 81006
    - Jamaica
      - #111 Title: Woman Talk: Caribbean Dub Poetry
        - Performer: Elaine Thomas, Breeze, Anita Stewart, Afua, Louise Bennett (Box 43)
          Side 1: Get Back, Respect, Politician, Beggin' is a Ting, Color Bar
          Side 2: Reality, Desperation Poem, Mother Francis, South Afrika, Dutty Tuff, Dutty Dub
          Record Label: Heartbeat Records, HB-25
    - Jewish
      - #112 Title: Chants du Ghetto (Box 43)
        Side 1: Oy a Nacht a sheyne, Yisrolik, Ver der ershter vet lachn, Shtil di Nacht iz oysgeshternt, Tsipele, Farvos iz der Himl geven nechtn loyter?, Sheyn bin ich sheyn, Oyfdem Zamd fun Negev
        Side 2: A Mame's Nign, Findjan, Oy dortn dortn ibern Vaserl, Frunze verde, Noch a Giezele Tey, Yididsh, Motele
        Record Label: Folkways Records, Le Chant du Monde, FWX-M-53558
      - #113 Title: Romanzas y Cantigas Sefardies
        - Performer: Joaquin Diaz (Box 43)
          Side 1: A la una yo nazi, Caminando por la plaza, La rosa enflorece, Desde hoy la mi madre, Una hija tiene el rey, Mam yo no tengo visto, Hija ma mi querida, Dize la nuestra novia, Esta montaa
          Side 2: Una pastora, Mi padre era de Francia, Arvoles yoran, A la nana, Avre este abajour, Levanteisme madre, Avre tu puerta cerrada, Durme durme, Buena semana
          Record Label: Movieplay, S-26117
      - #114 Title: Jewish Folk Songs
        - Performer: Martha Schlamme (Box 43)
          Side 1: Chanuke, O Chanuke!, Geh ich mir Spatzieren, Mai Komashmo Lon, Shein bin ich shein, Tum-balalayka, Die Mesinke, Sug mir du shein Meidele, Dire-gelt
          Side 2: A pintele, Oy Dortn Dortn Ibern Vaserl, Freilach, Partizaner Lid, Zog Nit Keynmol, Zhankoye, Tif in Veldele, Die Machetunem
          Record Label: Vanguard, VRS-9011
    - Mexico (Box 44)
      - #115 Title: 4 Copas
        - Performer: Lola Beltran (Box 44)
          Side 1: Cuatro copas, Llegando a t, Que bonito que bonito, La espiga, Cuando nadie te quiera, Vmonos
          Side 2: Nube pasajera, La noche y t, Lo nuestro se acab, Adorado tormento, Siempre hace fro, Paloma negra
          Record Label: Peerless, LPL 183
      - #116 Title: Soledad Bravo
        - Performer: Soledad Bravo, Rafael Alberti (Box 44)
          Side 1: A Cadiz base extranjera, Rota oriental Spain, Ven mi amor, Al pueblo de Brasil, Balada del posible regreso, Balada del parana, Yo mataba a los murcielagos
          Side 2: Coplas de Juan Panadero, Juan Panadero en Amrica, Que trata de Espaa, A la soledad me vine, A Pablo Neruda en el corazn, Tarde de otoo
          Record Label: Gamma, GX 01-1145
      - #117 Title: Soledad Bravo Vol. 4
        - Performer: Soledad Bravo (Box 44)
          Side 1: Palabras de amor, Coplas de Martin Ferro, Gottingen, Los mineros de Asturias, Nana Meridea
          Side 2: Apelo, El corralero, Gre de Lyon, A jangada voltou so, Yo me vi rodeando el mundo
          Record Label: Gamma, GX 01-746
      - #118 Title: Soledad Bravo
        - Performer: Soledad Bravo (Box 44)
          Side 1: La vida no vale nada, Yo pisare las calles nuevamente, A Salvador Allende en su combate por la vida, Sueo con serpientes
          Side 2: Campo de amor, El tiempo el implacable, El colibri, Esta cancin, Mariposas
          Record Label: Gamma, GX 01-1179
      - #119 Title: Un grito, una cancin, una esperanza, testimonios rebeldes
        - Performer: Jose de Molina Jose (Box 44)
          Side 1: Amrica latina canta, Las elecciones, los gorilas, Halcn colea colea, El gallito trovador (Sobre un tema popular oaxaqueo
          Side 2: De la mano del viento, La serpiente verde, Al general, Cura y guerillero, Canto por genero Vsquez R., Despedida
          Record Label: Nueva Voz (Latinoamericana), JS-05
      - #120 Title: Musica de la Costa Chica de Guerrero y Oasaca (Box 44)
        Side 1: Ya te he dicho, Vibrorita del mar, La paloma y el jarabe Oaxacado, Tragedia de Prisco Sanchez
        Side 2: Con cuidadito, La Yerbabuena, Maria Palitos, Chilena de pinotepa nacional, Mariquita mia
        Record Label: Instituto Nacional de Antropologa e Historia, MC 0828
      - #121 Title: Al cancionero popular
        - Performer: Amparo Ochoa, Los Folkloristas (Box 44)
          Side 1: El barzon, Tierra humeda, A que les tiras cuando sueas Mexicano, El negro Manuel Antonio, Bola Suriana de la muerte de Emiliano Zapata, La madicin de malinche
          Side 2: Jugar a la vida, La prietta clara, Como tu, Cancin para despertar a un negro, Mi abuelo, Quiero
          Record Label: Discos Pueblo, DP1006
      - #122 Title: Canta con los nios
        - Performer: Amparo Ochoa (Box 44)
          Side 1: Pas con rey, Los tres gorrioncitos, El papalote azul, El gurisito, Mi arbolito, Protesta infantil
          Side 2: Sapin sapen, El mundo al reves, El vaquerito, Cancin para mi nio, El sembrador, Himno pionero
          Record Label: Discos Pueblos, DP-1048
      - #123 Title: Cronica mexicana
        - Performer: Judith Reyes (Box 44)
          Side 1: La Salinidad, Corrido de Arturo Gamiz, Corrido de Santo Domingo, Los nios trabajadores
          Side 2: Gorilita gorilon, La ocupacin militar de la universidad, Cancin del politecnico, La tragedia de la Plaza de las Tres Culturas, Marcha de los Caidos
          Record Label: Le Noveau Chansonnier International, Le Chant du Monde, LDX-74421
      - #124 Title: Canciones mexicanas en la voz inolvidable
        - Performer: Lucha Reyes (Box 44)
          Side 1: El herradero, Cancin mexicana, La Panchita, Mujer ladina, As somos en Jalisco, Tlaquepaque
          Side 2: Caminito de contreras, Ay Jalisco no te rajes, Por un amor, El Juan, Maanita, Ay mamita
          Record Label: RCA Victor, MKL-1120
      - #125 Title: De Tlatelolco a Tlatelolco (Box 44)
        Side 1: Volveremos (Testimonios de carteles, consignas, canciones de Mxico 68.), Un lugar de Javier Snchez Arreglo: "Los Nakos", 2 de octubre de Vctor Sanen
        Side 2: Matanza Templo Mayor (Ao 1521, Texto indgena), Ultimos das de Tlatelolco (Ao 1521, texto indgena), 6.10 P.M. Tlatelolco 1968. Un minuto de silencio. De Mascarones., Homenaje a los estudiantes mexicanos de Angel Parra ( Chile)
        Record Label: Mascarones, L.P.M. 03
    - Nicaragua
      - #126 Title: Yo soy de un pueblo sencillo
        - Performer: Luis E. Mejia Godoy (Box 44)
          Side 1: Primero de enero, El inventario, Pobrecito mi Chipote, Para recordar, Tininiska
          Side 2: Dos canciones de amor para el otoo, Venencia, Mi venganza personal, Opino, Yo soy de un pueblo sencillo
          Record Label: ENIGRAC, MC-021
    - Palestine
      - #127 Title: Palestine Lives: Songs from the Struggle of the people of Palestine (Songs interspersed by interviews) (Box 44)
        Side 1: Beladi (Motherland), The Revolutionairies' Debt, The Rising Tide, The Testament of a Martyr, The Road of Dignity, Fedayee (Freedom Fighter), Palestinian Arab
        Side 2: Take Me With You, The March of Our People, The Revolutionaries' Pledge, The Wedding of Victory, Blood United Us, Al-Assifa (The Storm), Over the Hill, If I Should Fall, I Am Enduring
        Record Label: Paredon, P-1022
    - Puerto Rico
      - #128 Title: Basta Ya Revolucin: Letra y Musica de Roy Brown
        - Performer: Roy Brown (Box 44)
          Side 1: Antonio muri de un balazo, Pal viejo y que adivine, El negrito bonito, Lamento neoyorquino
          Side 2: Falsos constructores, Al hombre nuevo (A la brigada de la zona minera), Soy puertoriqueo, Vengan mis amigos, Descargo Num. 51
          Record Label: Disco Libre, L.P. 002
      - #129 Title: Puerto Rico 2010
        - Performer: Frank Ferrer (Box 44)
          Side 1: Tema, Camilo Torres, Yo tu, Hemos dicho basta, Ya se van
          Side 2: A desalambrar y a rescatar, Paloma, Pa los obreros, La borinquera, Tema
          Record Label: TLD-001
      - #130 Title: Tengo Puerto Rico en mi corazon (I Have Puerto Rico in My Heart)
        - Performer: Pepe y Flora (Box 44)
          Side 1: Que Bonita Bandera, Culebras y vieques, Puerto Rico tiene minas, Yo Quiero, Preciosa, En un pueblito
          Side 2: Controversia, Orgullosa, Senor inversionista, Volveremos, Borinquen, Cuchifritos
          Record Label: Paredon, P1005
      - #131 Title: Aqu se hable espaol!
        - Performer: Pedro Pietri (Box 44)
          Side 1: Aqu se hable espaol, Puerto Rican obituary, Himno de Papa Dios, Sex and the Virgin Mary
          Side 2: Suicide Note of a Cockroach, The Rise and Fall of the Avon Lady, The Broken English Dream, The Blue Uniform
          Record Label: Discos Coqui LP 1203
    - Spain
      - #132 Title: Cantos de la resistencia (Box 44)
        Side 1: Cancion de Bourg-Madame, Ya se fue el verano, Sin pan, Desde que Franco y la Falange, Muerte en la catedral
        Side 2: En Espaa, las flored, Y son tiempos de bonanza, La herba de los caminos, Cancion de paz, Una cancion
      - #133 Title: Songs of the Spanish civil war, v. 2
        - Performer: Woody Guthrie, Ernst Busch, Bart van der Schelling, Exiles Chorus (Box 44)
          Side 1: Jarama, On the Jarama front, Ballad of the XI brigade, Hans Beimler, Comerade, The Thaelmann-Column
          Side 2: Santa Espina, Sevillanos, The road to Aviles, La guardia rossa, Wie hinterm Draht, La joven guardia, Au devant de la vie
          Record Label: Folkways, FH 5437
          Insert with lyrics.
    - Venezuela
      - #134 Title: Venezuela, guerriglia
        - Performer: Douglas Bravo (Box 44)
          Side 1: Messaggi di guerriglieri della montagna ai combattenti della citt, Todos los trabajadores, Corrido de Argimiro Gabaldon, Corrido de Fabricio Ojeda
          Side 2: Altri messaggi e saluto del Comandante Raul, Viva las faln, Campesino obrero estudiante, Las clases dominantes
          Record Label: Archivi Sonori, SdL AS/6
    - Pop, Folk, Labor movement, Protest (Box 45)
      - #135 Title: Farewell, Angelina
        - Performer: Joan Baez (Box 45)
          Side 1: Farewell Angelina, Daddy You've Been On My Mind, It's All Over Now Baby Blue, The Wild Mountain Thyme, Ranger's Command, Colours
          Side 2: Satisfied Mind, The River in the Pines, Pauvre Rutebouef, Sagt Mir wo die Blumen sind, A Hard Rain's a-Gonna Fall
          Record Label: Vanguard-9200
      - #136 Title: Joan Baez, Volume 2
        - Performer: Joan Baez (Box 45)
          Side 1: Wagoner's Lad, The Trees They Do Grow High, The Lily of the West, Silkie, Engine, Once I Knew a Pretty Girl, Lonesome Road
          Side 2: Banks of the Ohio, Pal of Mine, Barbara Allen, The Cherry Tree Carol, Old Blue, Railroad Boy, Plaisir d'Amour
          Record Label: Vanguard, VRS-9004
      - #137 Title: Elaine Brown
        - Performer: Elaine Brown (Box 45)
          Side 1: No Time, Jonathan, Can't Go Back, All the Young and Fine Men, Until We're Free
          Side 2: I Know Who You Are, Child in the World, A Little Baby, And We Shall Meet Again
          Record Label: Black Forum, BF 458L
      - #138 Title: The Best of the Chad Mitchell Trio
        - Performer: Chad Mitchell Trio (Box 45)
          Side 1: Lizzie Borden, Hang on the Bell Nellie, The Great Historical Bum (The Bragging Song), Super Skier, The John Birch Society
          Side 2: The Ides of Texas - Don't Fence Me In, James James Morrison Morrison, Green Grow The Lilacs, Hello Susan Brown, The Unfortunate Man, You Can Tell The World
          Record Label: Kapp, KL-1334
      - #139 Title: To Be a Man
        - Performer: Len Chandler (Box 45)
          Side 1: To Be a Man, Feet First Baby, Nancy Rose, Bellevue, Missionary Stew #2, Keep on Keepin' On
          Side 2: Shadow Dream Chaser of Rainbows, Hide Your Heart Little Hippie, Roll Turn Spin, Time of the Tiger, Takin' Me Away From You Train, Quittin' Time
          Record Label: Columbia, CL 2459
      - #140 Title: Golden Apples of the Sun
        - Performer: Judy Collins (Box 45)
          Side 1: Golden Apples of the Sun, Bonnie Ship the Diamond, Little Brown Dog, Twelve Gates to the City, Christ Child Lullaby, Great Selchie of Shule Skerry
          Side 2: Tell Me Who I'll Marry, Fannerio, Crow on the Cradle, Lark in the Morning, Sing Hallelujah, Shule Aroon
          Record Label: Elektra, EKL-222
      - #141 Title: The Judy Collins Concert
        - Performer: Judy Collins (Box 45)
          Side 1: Winter Sky, The Last Thing on My Mind, Tear Down the Walls, Bonnie Boy Is Young, Me and My Uncle, Wild Rippling Water, The Lonesome Death of Hattie Carroll
          Side 2: My Ramblin' Boy, Red-Winged Blackbird, Coal Tattoo, Cruel Mother, Bottle of Wine, Medgar Evers Lullaby, Hey Nelly Nelly
          Record Label: Elektra, EKL-280
      - #142 Title: Mean Mothers Independent Women's Blues, Volume 1
        - Performer: Ida Cox, Lil Green, Mary Dixon, Bessie Brown, Bertha Idaho, Maggie Jones, Billie Holiday, Lil Armstrong, Susie Edwards, Gladys Bentley, Harlem Hannah, Blue Lou Barker, Rosa Henderson, Rosetta Howard, Bernice Edwards, Martha Copeland (Box 45)
          Side 1: Good Time Mama, Ain't Much Good in the Best of Men Nowadays, You Ain't Gonna Feed in My Pasture Now, Oh Yeah, Long Tall Mama, How Much Can I Stand?, You Can't Sleep in My Bed, Move It on Out of Here
          Side 2: Can't Be Bothered with No Sheik, Keep Your Nose Out of Mama's Business, Or Leave me Alone, I Don't Dig You Jack, Come Easy Go Easy, One Hour Mama, Why Don't You Do Right, Baby Get Lost
          Record Label: Rosetta Records, RR 1300
      - #143 Title: FTA! Songs of the GI Resistance
        - Performer: Barbara Dane, Bill Frederick, Janus, Fred Gardner, Pete Seeger, active-duty GIs (Box 45)
          Side 1: Join the GI Movement, Hallelujah I'm a Bum, Ballad of Richard Campos, Go Tell it on the Mountain, Just Another Day, We Shall Not be Moved
          Side 2: Resistance hymn, Insubordination, Last Drink with Don, Bring 'em Home
          Record Label: Paredon P1003
          Insert with information about the resistance movement. Recorded at Fort Hood, Texas, Fort Benning, Georgia., and Fort Bragg, North Carolina.
      - #144 Title: Julie Felix
        - Performer: Julie Felix (Box 45)
          Side 1: Masters of War, The Old Maid's Song, Hey Nelly Nelly (Hey Willie Willie), Cu-Cu-Ru-Cu, Tarry Town, Aunt Rhode, Pastures of Plenty
          Side 2: Tell Old Bill, Ship in the Sky, Buttermilk Hill, Sally Don't You Grieve, Don't Think Twice It's All Right, The Riddle Song, Plane Crash at Los Gatos
          Record Label: DECCA, LK4626
      - #145 Title: The Freedom Singers Sing of Freedom Now!
        - Performer: Freedom Singers, John Lewis (speech) (Box 45)
          Side 1: We are soldiers in the army, Speech by John Lewis, They laid Medgar Evers in his grave, Soon-a will be done, Come by here
          Side 2: I'm a Demonstratin' G.I. From Fort Bragg, Oginga odinga, We'll Never Turn Back (Theme song of the Mississippi Summer Project), The Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee, Oh Freedom, This Light of Mine
          Record Label: Mercury, MG 20924
      - #146 Title: Joe Glazer Sings Labor Songs
        - Performer: Joe Glazer (Box 45)
          Side 1: We Shall Not be Moved, Miner's Strawberries, Hard Times in the Mill, We are Building a Strong Union, The Mill was Made of Marble, Union Maid, Roll the Union on, That's All
          Side 2: Solidarity Forever, It Could be a Wonderful World, Union train, Joe Hill, John Henry, Automation, Too Old to Work, We've Got a Lot of Work to do
          Record Label: Collector Records, 1918
      - #147 Title: Working People Gonna Rise
        - Performer: Beverly Grant, Human Condition (Box 45)
          Side 1: Things ain't what they used to be, Janie's Janie, Charlie's song, Chain reaction, Feel good
          Side 2: Father, Mama, I remember, Uncle Sam, Clifford Glover, Working people gonna rise
          Record Label: Paredon, P-1024
          Insert with biographical information about the performers and Paredon Records.
      - #148 Title: Hazel and Alice
        - Performer: Hazel and Alice (Box 45)
          Side 1: Mining Camp Blues, Hello Stranger, The Green Rolling Hills of West Virginia, A Few More Years Shall Roll, Two Soldiers, The Sweetest Gift a Mother's Smile, Tomorrow I'll be Gone
          Side 2: My Better Years, Custom-Made Woman Blues, Don't Put Her Down You Helped Put Her There, You Gave Me a Song, Pretty Bird, Gallop to Kansas
          Record Label: Rounder Records, 0027
      - #149 Title: The Original Read-in for Peace in Vietnam
        - Performer: Stanley Kauffmann, chairman, edited by Rosaline Wells & Louis Menashe (Box 45)
          Side 1: Dr. Oscar Sachs, Stanley Kauffmann, Ossie Davis, Ruby Dee, Alan Dugan, Alfred Kazin, Susan Sontag, Galway Kinnell, Viveca Lindfors, Denise Levertov, William Gibson, Jules Feiffer, Louis Untermeyer, William Styron, Maureen Stapleton
          Side 2: Tony Randall, Hortense Calisher, Robert Lowell, Lenore Marshall, Arthur Miller, Joel Oppenheimer, William Melvin Kelley, Walter Lowenfels, Norman Mailer, Fritz Weaver, Muriel Rukeyser, Bernard Malamud, Stanley Kunitz, Lillian Hellman, Harvey Swados
          Record Label: Broadside Records, BR 452
          Insert with notes and the text of the speechs.
      - #150 Title: The Last Poets
        - Performer: The Last Poets (Box 45)
          Side 1: Run Nigger, On the Subway, Niggers Are Scared of Revolution, Black Thighs, Gashman, Wake Up Niggers
          Side 2: New York New York, Joners Comin' Down, Just Because, Black Wish, When the Revolution Comes, Two Little Boys, Surprises
          Record Label: Douglas 3
      - #151 Title: Boston Ride
        - Performer: Lilith (Box 45)
          Side 1: Funky Tale, (Everytime I turn Around) Back in Love Again, Pick Up the Pieces, Boston Ride
          Side 2: Nomad, Gold and Silver, Long Train Runnin', Too Late
          Record Label: Galaxia
      - #152 Title: Bad Lads and Hard Cases, British Ballads of Crime and Criminals
        - Performer: Ewan MacColl, Peggy Seeger (Box 45)
          Side 1: Turpin Hero, Spence Broughton, Ivor, The Bonnie Banks of Airdrie, Superintendent Barratt, Barratty-Parratty, Go Down You Murderer, Van Damien's Land
          Side 2: Whiskey in the Jar, Bill Brown, The Banks of the Royal Canal, The Black Velvet Band, Hard Case, The Ballad of Bentley and Craig, Treadmill Song, Gilderoy
          Record Label: Riverside, RLP 12-632
      - #153 Title: Helene Martin
        - Performer: Helene Martin (Box 45)
          Side 1: Auberge toi et moi, Il y avait tant de muguet, Le velo, Rue de chateau, Baptiste des Merveilles, Chant des Vauriens
          Side 2: Ainsi Prague, Le Plaisir dieu, J'attends j'attendrai, L'homme en bleu, Bel-abbes, S'il est un beau jour
          Record Label: Disques Ads, 33 VS 591
      - #154 Title: Canciones de Espaa
        - Performer: Germaine Montero (Box 45)
          Side 1: Los Cuatros Muleros, Los Contrabandistas de Ronda, Nana, Paso Rio, No hay quien pueda, Eres Alta y Delgada, El baile de Avila
          Side 2: Ya se van los pastores, Jotas, Asturiana, Folia de San Vicente de la Barquera, Corrocloclo, Fandango, Gallegada, Con las Abejas
          Record Label: Vanguard, VRS-9050
      - #155 Title: Chante les grandes chansons de Pierre Mac Orlan, Volume 2
        - Performer: Germaine Montero (Box 45)
          Side 1: Fanny de Lanninon, Le dpart des joyeaux, La chanson de bagatelle, Nelly, Le Pont du Nord, La Rue Saint-Jacques
          Side 2: La chanson de Margaret, La belle de mai, crit sur les murs, a n'a pas d'importance, Tortuga
          Record Label: EMI, ATX 145
      - #156 Title: Jacques Prvert dit par Germaine Montero
        - Performer: Germaine Montero (Box 45)
          Side 1: Fleurs et couronnes, La pche a la baleine, Pour toi mon amour, La visite au muse, Chanson de l'oiseleur, Barbara, Les feuilles mortes, La couleur locale
          Side 2: Rue de seine, Le cauchemar du chauffeur de taxi, Cet amour, Le dsepoir est assis sur un bang, Nuages, Chanson pour vous, Le gardien du phare aime beaucoup trop les oiseaux, Promenade de Picasso
          Record Label: Vega, V 30 M 961
      - #157 Title: Lament on the Death of a Bullfighter and other poems and songs of Frederico Garca Lorca (Box 45)
        Side 1: Llanto por Ignacio Snchez Mejas (La Cogida y la muerte, La sangre derramada, Cuerpo Performer: Germaine Montero presente, Alma ausente), Cancin de Belisa, La guitarra, Las tres hojas, Poema del cante jondo (El grito, El silencio)
        Side 2: Las Morillas de Jan, Prendimiento de Antoito el Camborio en al camino de Sevilla, Muerte de Antoito el Camborio, Despierte la novia, La casada infiel, La seora zapatera, Romance de la Guardia Civil espaola
        Record Label: Vanguard, VRS-9055
      - #158 Title: Monmartre la nuit
        - Performer: Germaine Montero (Box 45)
          Side 1: Jazz Band, Je voulais des soleils, C'est a Hambourg, Les beaux enfants, Complainte de Jack L'eventreur, La chanson de Marianne, Chanson des Saintes Maries de la Mer
          Side 2: Paris Canaille, La bar de la femme sans tette, Le chat de la voisine, Ne fais pas comme moi, Je pense a toi, Pauvre Ruteboeuf, La complainte du bon pasteur
          Record Label: Vanguard, VRS-9082
      - #159 Title: Songs from Mother Courage and Songs of Parisian Nights
        - Performer: Germaine Montero (Box 45)
          Side 1: Chanson de Mere Courage, Marche de la victoire, Chanson de la fraternisation, Chanson de Saloman, Marche de la victoire, Berceuse, Cahnson de la grande capitulation
          Side 2: La fille de Londres, La chanson de Margaret, Belleville - Menilmontant, Les enfants qui s'aiment, En sortant de l'ecole, Chanson pour les enfants l'hiver, Et la fte continue, Et puis aprs, Tha-ma-ra-boum-dee-he
          Record Label: Vanguard, VRS-9022
      - #160 Title: Fire in the Rain
        - Performer: Holly Near (Box 45)
          Side 1: Fire in the Rain, Once or Twice, I Got Trouble, No Loss of Pride, Sit With Me
          Side 2: Working Woman, Foolish Notion, Ain't No Where You Can Run, Wrap the Sun Around You, Voices, Golden Thread
          Record Label: Redwood Records, RR402
      - #161 Title: Hang in There
        - Performer: Holly Near (Box 45)